[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[Crowd cheers]
[Referee] Pre
Ale
[Caster] Jonghyun Kim
There's an attack going on.
- [Jonghyun] Ah!
- [Beep!]
[Commentator] Roger
Blocking and stabbing are successful.
[Referee] Alt
Atakpalli, report tshu
[Caster]
What's wrong with your ankle?
Today, Kim Jong-hyun
I can't move forward.
- [Heavy music]
- [Car horn]
[Hannah moans]
- Are you okay?
- Yes
[Caster] Step speed
As it falls, the motion increases.
- Many loopholes are being exposed.
- [Jonghyun] Ah!
- [Referee] Atak tshu
- [Caster] Roger scores
[Rough breathing]
[Dongju] What are you doing? Hey, wake up
[Commentator] The current opponent is
Because I'm left handed
The direction from which the attack comes
I need to read it carefully.
[Audience cheers and applause]
[Referee] Anggard
pre
Ale
[Jonghyun’s moans]
- [Beep!]
- [Jonghyun’s moans]
[Roaring roar]
- [Heavy music]
- Huh?
[Jonghyun] Ugh, uh...
What's going on?
Something unusual happened
[Jonghyun’s heavy breathing]
[Commentator] Ah, this knife
Breaking down in an instant
mask down
Looks like it was infiltrated
[Caster] Ah, the situation is
It doesn't look very good.
Oh, that's too bad
Jonghyun Kim
eye injury
It shouldn't be serious
Oh...
[Coach] Jonghyun, are you okay?
[Referee/English] Are you okay?
Can you continue?
[Coach] Are you sure it’s okay?
I can do it
I can do it, I can do it
I'm the best
[Referee] Anggard
pre
Ale
[intense music]
[A man's spirit]
[Man's scream]
[Dongju’s spirit]
[Clap]
[Man 1’s spirit]
[Man 2 moans]
[Together] Ugh!
[Man] Ugh!
Ouch!
[Vroom Vroom]
[Bang!]
[Seokchun] Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, I got hurt.
[Jijijik]
[Jonghyun’s moans]
[Seokchun’s laughter]
Ah, look at this stupid bastard.
Hey, how is this scary?
Hey, is this scary?
scared? uh?
Hey, where did that Superman go earlier?
Where is the flying Superman? uh?
I'm leaving in a hurry
Come here, okay? Come here
[Bang!]
[Motorcycle engine sound]
Ugh...
child, Mr.
[Exciting music]
Hey, you bastard! Mr.
I missed it
Ah
Hey
Even afraid of needles
What are you doing to my child?
Is this your kid? I didn't know
It's okay
Because you just need to know from now on
Now I have to pay for hitting my child.
You little squirrel
Squirrel?
This bastard, Mr.
This bastard
You bastard
[nervous music]
[Seokchun’s moans]
*Baby...
[Dongju] Wake up
Because it's just the beginning
[Bang!]
[Man] Hey!
[Squeak!]
[Jonghyun] Yoon Dong-ju!
[dark music]
[Seokchun] Ah, President Min
Hey, hey!
[Jonghyun’s moans]
[Jooyoung] Are you dead?
Ah...
It's alive
What do you think?
How does it feel to be stretched out on the asphalt?
Is it different from being in the ring?
No matter how much you guys
I need to use my head and make a plan
The result is like this
Why are you having such a hard time buying it?
[Dongju] That’s my strength
You dirty, bad bastard.
[Jooyoung] Kids’ pranks
Just do it in the ring
I told you
Implementing justice?
Don't even think about doing something like that.
we are
I'm risking my life
today
It's going to be a very impressive day.
[Dongju groans with difficulty]
look forward to it
jab
Kids kidding?
Risking your life is
Same goes for the ring.
[Seokchun] Hey, I think you guys are lucky.
Hey, you puppy, get out of the way if you don’t want to die.
[Sound of car door closing]
Are you okay?
you?
What about Hannah?
I have to go find Hannah.
[Man] Hey!
huh?
wow
[Car engine sound]
There will be a scratch on your pretty face
Hey, you idiots
What are you doing!
Get out of the car!
move quickly
Hey, get your stuff, let's go!
hurry up
[Exciting music]
[Men's spirit]
let's go
[Dongju] It’s Hannah!
[Together] Jihanna!
- It's Hannah.
- [Dongju] It’s Hannah!
[heavy music]
[Dongju] Hannah, Hannah
[Jonghyun] Hanna, Ji Hanna!
There is no
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
It's Hannah!
Sergeant Kim
Dongju, are you okay? What about motorcycles?
[Jonghyun] Team leader, are you okay?
I don't know, I think I dozed off for a moment.
That's not important, what about Inspector Ji?
Oh, my phone still doesn't work.
I have no way to contact Hanna.
What should I do?
Mr. [Mansik]
Why on earth are you doing this, Mr.
[Daeyong] Everything in this area is like that.
On a nearby base station communication pylon
I think there's a problem
It takes a long time to recover.
After the riot squad car had already left
Something happened
They decided to lock me up here
He hit Ado.
in container
Doesn't it have a tracker?
Ah, this is it
It's broken
[Mansik] Hey
We were completely screwed
Jaehong is also not in good condition.
I was taken to the hospital
I feel like my back hurts
[Daeyong] Just past the Jungdong Tunnel
Seodong, Cheoli-dong, Cheolsam-dong
There are many ways out
From the communication network to the surrounding CCTV
If you see it cut off
They are very thorough.
If you want to catch it today
I think we need more troops.
Can you do it?
[Nervous music]
Still need to find it
Hannah would be there.
The luggage is in the back seat
thank you
[Mansik] Over there
I went to Jaehong
I'll go to the office and request military support.
Hey, hurry up and join the team leader.
Go to the hospital and get treatment first.
What are you doing? I told you to go to the hospital
Jonghyun Kim
I need to find Hannah
Find someone with that body
I will find Hannah
[Jonghyun] Then you can ride too
no time
Come out, get out of the way
Okay, get in, I'll drive.
If you want to find Hannah, come to your senses first.
To Cheori-dong and Seodong
The paths diverge
Stop the car here for a moment
[Click - Turn Signal Light]
Which way did it go?
eww!
[Together] Huh?
[Dongju] Huh?
It's Hannah's
- [Jonghyun] I’ll look here.
- [Dongju] Yes
[Jonghyun] Yoon Dong-ju, Yoon Dong-ju!
I found it
I think it's over there
[Interesting music]
[Jonghyun] This is Hannah’s, right?
That's right
[Jonghyun] Wait a minute, wait a minute
Stop the car
My phone is all broken too
Right?
Ah...
let's go quickly
Come quickly
[Exciting music]
[Jonghyun sighs]
[click - car door]
Hey, what are you doing!
Move quickly, move quickly, quickly
[Organization member] No, a little...
[Seokchun] Well, check the items well.
[Organization member] Go quickly!
Well, we have to get it all down before the sun sets.
[Squeak - Container]
open it quickly
Is there any problem with the item?
Check this carefully
Hey, more cars are coming.
[Oncoming car engine sound]
[Jonghyun] So they can’t be traced
Share things
I feel like I'm scattered
[Dongju] Just by looking at the tire tracks
I don't think it's just one or two.
'4131'?
What is this?
[Meaningful music]
[Jonghyun] It’s like the car number
I need to find this car quickly
Wait a minute
[Beep-Cellphone]
[Call connection tone]
Yes, team leader
That truck ending in 4131
I would like to check the vehicle, please.
yes
First, go back to the office
Let’s check all the live CCTVs.
[Jonghyun] Team leader, vehicle inquiry...
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Dongju] I’m getting a call.
The police chief is calling.
[Complete/small] Cut it off, cut it off, cut it off
[Dongju] Ah, but why is that?
I don't have time right now, what about support?
You said something like Jiwon and fell asleep.
Hey, if I get caught now, I can’t do anything.
Hands and feet will all be tied
This bastard
The commissioner isn’t answering the phone?
[Voice guidance] Customer is calling...
He doesn't get it either.
Oh, Sergeant Kim doesn't get it either.
Hey, let's go take a listen.
[humorous music]
[Panel] These are real, Mr.
You are Go Man-sik
Do you really know where you went?
Yes, I saw it at the tunnel site.
After that...
What after that?
I haven't seen you since then, yeah
I'll catch it right away when I see it.
Huh? excuse me! Go Man-sik
Go Man-sik! Stop, stop...
- Hey, Go Man-sik...
- [Mansik’s sigh]
- Stop it, you bastard, tsk.
- [Substitute] Yes, yes
gone, gone
[Mansik] 96 wave 4131, it’s a cannon vehicle
However, Inspector Shin went to the traffic department.
I asked you to figure out the route.
Something will come out
[Dongju]
Yes? Jaehong went to the hospital.
[Mansik] There, there, there, there
[Dongju] Huh? brother
Hey, is your back okay?
They say it’s not very good?
Oh, not much, just a little crooked.
Are you okay?
[Jonghyun] Still in the hospital
Isn’t it supposed to be there?
I need to find Inspector Ji quickly.
I can't just lie down
I should help where I can
That makes me feel at ease
[Mansik] Yes, somehow quickly
I need to find out the location of the police station.
Let's move on and talk
Ride fast
- [Interesting Music]
- Ta
- Shall we ride again?
- [Mansik] Ta
[Boom! Bang bang!]
[Pawn shop owner] Oh, who are you?
Oh, what time is it?
[Boom! Bang bang!]
Oh, who are you? Tsk
Oh my, really
What are these lesser-looking guys?
[Pawnshop owner]
What is Bongchang in the middle of the night?
Sleep is my life
I've been dreaming of getting married for a while
What's going on with all the little brats?
[Mansik] Something like that happened.
Well, what do you want to know?
Is this a pawn shop? Heungsinsoje
Are you a criminal case? Pawnbroker system, huh?
What are you doing?
These are quite diverse, huh?
In the country that won the Nobel Prize
Uncultured, shallow, tsk
Just wait, I said I would contact you.
[Ding Dong]
[Interesting music]
[Jaehong] This is car 4131.
This was taken at the Seodong intersection.
From here
I traveled on National Route 23.
where did it fall
Nothing was caught on camera
[Mansik] Ah, oh, oh...
If it's National Route 23, it's over there.
Ah, there are so many ways to get lost.
Those are all side roads.
It's hard to check them all
[Jaehong] On CCTV
Trucks traveling on Route 23
I have to look for everything.
in trucks and containers
To move all the cargo
It would take a lot of trucks.
Where do those trucks come from?
I think it would be good to find out
[Dongju] What about Oh Jong-gu?
Probably not there
[Mansik] Oh, yeah
Truck drivers in Ojong-gu
Right now at the city hall protest site
Everyone is out
Ah, what should I do first?
I can't figure it out at all
[Wing - Cell Phone]
- [Pawnshop owner] This...
- [Mansik] Tsk
I know, I know, tsk
[Pawnshop owner clears his throat]
This
This?
This...
This, this, this
This~
[Call end sound]
- [Mansik] Are you here?
- [Pawn Shop Owner] You're right.
Gwangse wants to stow away
I contacted the broker.
Where?
Dageumhang 4 o'clock, Geumdongho
First, let’s ask the bald eagle.
[Gwangse/Crying] Geumdonga
Where are you? Really
I came
Oh, sir, where are you, really?
[whistle]
Geumdonga
Is it gilt bronze?
[whistle]
Uh, take a look at this
Uh...
Hey, Gwangse
[Deng - sound effect]
Why do snakes come out at night?
Whistle and damn it
- Are you here?
- [Mansik] Nice to meet you, right?
yes
[Mansik] Be careful
[Gwangse] Ah, sir, here
How did you know this, Mr.
- [Humorous music]
- [Scream]
Uh, uh, what should I do with this?
[Dongju] I’m disappointed
Still, I thought you were on our side.
Everyone is here
Hmm...
It's cute
Oh, that
We sell it
Did you get it from Minjooyoung?
No, no, this, this
I bought it, I bought it
Uh, that, Vietnam, lives in Vietnam.
A gift for my daughter
[Gwangse’s laughter]
There's a mustache here, haha...
No, not that one.
What's in there
[Creepy sound effect]
[Joyful music]
- [Dongju] Hey, hey, hey
- [Mansik] Catch it!
[Dongju] Hey, hey
[Gwangse] Ugh, ugh!
[Gulp] Ah!
[Mansik] Ah, Mr.
[Jonghyun] What is it?
[Gwangse] Uh, uh...
[Mansik] This bastard, this, this
Do do do now to the medicine, Mr.
Hey, the distribution of drug raw materials
About, huh?
- [Together] 10 years
- [만식] 어, 그래
- 새끼야, 10년, 10년
- [광세] 마, 마...
이거 마약, 마약 그런 거 아니에요
이게 그때
감기에 걸려 가지고, 이게
꺽! Wow~
[Gulp]
[Dongju] We don’t have time right now
Are you really not going to talk?
[Mansik] Oh, stop drinking.
How long is it?
It needs to be diluted like this, really.
How much medicine did I take?
What if I die!
[Mansik] Hey, I’m dying because I’m full of water.
Come on, stop drinking, answer me
Oh, leave it alone.
Drink a lot, drink a lot
[Gwangse’s laughter]
But I don't drink water when I play
Do you know why?
If you drink water and make a mistake and get hit in the stomach
[Creepy sound effect]
Because the organ explodes
intestinal rupture
It hurts enough to kill me
Ha!
Ah, I ate it all
Oh, I, ah, I'm full
I have to stop eating now
Okay then tell me now
I don't feel like playing around anymore
[Jonghyun] Everything I know
Don't leave anything out
Then this time
I promise you will protect me
Now I risk my life too
Because I can't do it anymore
Huh? uh
Huh? uh? uh?
Uh, uh
With Japanese kids
All I heard was that there was a deal.
[Mansik] Japan?
Are they Yakuza kids?
Where is the trading location?
[Meaningful music]
Golden rabbit!
Golden Rabbit will know, Golden Rabbit
In the past, that guy
With the Yakuza guys
I was in charge of the transaction.
[Dongju] Like that
Are you going to keep your mouth shut?
the business you managed
Oh Jong-gu took it all
You're broke
No, but still
Are you loyal to Minjooyoung?
Are you still on trial?
They say they continue to exercise their right to remain silent.
Then apply to you
all charges
You will be found guilty.
Min Joo-young's criminal charges
You will overwrite it
It must be hard to see your little brother, Silver Rabbit.
Well, it will only come out when I die.
You met Minjooyoung, right?
[eerie music]
What did you do to my brother?
not dead yet
So
Shhh...
to open my mouth
Come find my brother
[Boom! - Moon]
I think Minjooyoung came and went.
I guess I did a good job controlling my mouth.
[Jonghyun] Probably because of my younger brother
I feel like I'm not opening my mouth
How do I find the silver rabbit?
Make an emergency order
It's been over a month
They say there isn't a single report.
It's already gone overseas.
Minjooyoung
Do you know its whereabouts?
Let's go first, look for Hannah.
[Mansik] Where do I start?
[Dongju sighs]
Haven't I been able to contact Hanna?
The day is coming to an end
- [Beep - Tinnitus]
-If it gets any later...
[Dongju] Ah
Hey, Kim Jonghyun
Don't talk nonsense
Hannah, I'm sure you'll be holding up well.
[Mansik] In times like this, even if it’s just location tracking
If you can...
The golden rabbit
Because I said it was a trading place.
I looked through that bastard’s data.
Let’s find all the areas where we were active.
It's going to take some time
There's no other way
I have to try everything I can now.
[Mansik] Yes
[Jonghyun] At the office
I couldn't get it all out.
Gwangsudae takes care of the rest.
How many bad things have you done?
Why is there so much?
For 20 years, I just ate and pooped.
There must be a smelly place
[Exciting music]
‘Sumang-dong, Okmi-gu’
Sumang-dong, Okmi-gu
- 'Daeri-dong'
- Where is Daeri-dong?
Ah, here
‘Bumyeong-dong, Jung-gu’
[Jaehong] Bumyeong-dong, Jung-gu
[Dongju] You too, look for something
If you don't want to become a bald eagle
[Baby laughing sound effect]
Then, can’t we do it after eating?
I've been running away since yesterday
Because I couldn’t eat anything
Oh, I'm so dizzy
Oh, if I order a bowl of seolleongtang
- [Gulp]
- I would really appreciate it.
Even the beeping sound stuck in my neck
It seems like it's going down suddenly
[Tak]
I won't kill you
I'm thankful just for being there
thank you
[Sarak - File]
[Beep - Tinnitus]
"Victory"
[Chiik - Truck]
[Calm music]
Ugh
'North Port, Choryeon 1-dong, Jung-gu'
Huh?
delicious
[Gwangse] Oh, what is it, just me
- [Jaehong] It’s delicious
- [Gwangse] Oh, ah!
[Dongju] Do it
[Noisy - Phone]
Ah, so what
Are you doing nothing right now?
[Daeyong] Oh, didn’t you see the news?
[Mansik] What news?
- [Noisy]
- There's a lot of chaos here.
[Detective] You didn’t even report the meeting.
If you do it so violently
What should I do?
Did I throw a soju bottle?
Why are you doing this? Calm down.
[Protester] No
Let me calm down now...
- [Noisy]
- Oh, I will believe it, I will believe it.
It is a clear challenge to public power.
For any reason...
no, so what
How hurt are you?
My forehead was torn by 1 cm.
Anyway, I'm out of my mind.
I can't support the troops.
- You...
- [Call end sound]
Man, I’m annoyed.
Just to make sure we don't catch any criminals, huh?
do do
I fell asleep after doing a show like that, Mr.
The police went missing
No investigation?
Oh, I can't eat because I'm hot.
I have to go now
Right now, just kill that commissioner...
Come in
I wasn't expecting it anyway.
We just need to find it
[Calm music]
[Mansik] But you these days
Why are you so calm, so uncharacteristic of you?
I knew it would be a long road, but
I'm holding on.
Because finding Hannah comes first.
After looking for
You can go wild then
I'll come back after getting some air.
- [clap - door]
- [Jingle jingle]
[Man-sik] Is he Dong-ju?
Now I feel a bit like a cop
Get some rest, right? It looks difficult
True
Ah, who are you talking to?
Just take a break
Because I feel like I'm going to collapse soon
[Poo - Boat horn]
Just check the sample first.
Due to circumstances
Share some things
I think I should send it to you.
The deal is here tonight
[Interpreter/Japanese] Just a sample for now
Please check first
[Stand up] I have to buy something for some reason.
I think I'll have to send it separately.
[Wake up] The deal is here tonight
[Stand up] I have a different promise.
[Stand up] It was definitely yesterday
I decided to receive the item, but
[Translator] I was supposed to receive the item yesterday.
I have a different promise...
I just had a situation
I think I said it
Isn’t it enough just to be sure of the item?
[Japanese] Sorry
[Stand up] There was a situation
Still, the thing is certain
[Stand up] The things of those who break their promises
How do I credit?
[Translator] I broke my promise
They say they can't trust things.
[sigh]
I'll give you a gift
[Japanese] I’ll give you a gift.
I
[Interpreter/Japanese] I
Indispensable to this organization
[Interpreter/Japanese] In this organization
indispensable
I'm an interpreter
[Japanese] I am an interpreter.
[dark music]
[Leo] Oh...
how
Can I trust this much?
Not enough?
What now?
[Standing up] Are you satisfied?
[Pawnshop owner] Atta
The bottom of my personality has grown so big that it’s swollen.
[Jonghyun] This is it
It's a place related to the golden rabbit.
[Mansik] Ah, there are a lot.
[Jaehong] Well, who owns it or who uses it?
Excluding the places that have changed
You might be able to guess a little more.
Then among these
A place where transactions can take place
Let’s mainly search for
[Mansik] Yeah, uh
If anything comes up, we'll contact you.
Oh, and take him, kid.
Inseong City, all the way to the side streets
Baby you know it all, it'll be quick
- [Dongju] Okay
- [Mansik] Go quickly
I have a mouthful now, please
I took a bite
Just one bite, I just have one bite and let’s go
Just one bite!
[Pawn shop owner] I’ll leave it to you.
[Nervous music]
[Seokchun] Hey, did you get all the stuff?
[Organization members] Yes, brother.
- [Seokchun] Good job
- [Organization members] Yes
[Seokchun] Hey, Mr.
Hey, this is expensive, huh?
Like a rat, on other people's things
Don't touch it carelessly
[Seokchun] Rat?
-Who are you talking about?
- [Nervous music]
[Leo] Who knows, you
squirrel
[Seokchun] Do you really want to die, huh?
- [Leo] Me?
- [Devil] Huh? what?
Wow, that's a good drink
- [English] Is it mine?
- [Seokchun] I, Mr.*
[Leo] Yes, sorry
Because this belongs to someone else
I'll get you something better.
[Russian] My black cat
[Leo's laughter]
[Devil] Someone else? who?
There is
[Devil] Huh? Who is it?
You won't tell me?
[Hannah] ‘30 caliber Russian made
'Estimated Tokarev'
'Russian mafia
'Possibility of black cat involvement'
[Russian] My black cat
[Gwangse] Ugh, ah...
What are you doing?
There is nothing
Are you up there?
I don't think it's here
let's go somewhere else
[Gwangse] Are you going to Jangpo?
Go out there
It's faster if you turn right.
Should we go to this area?
Which of those areas? where?
here
[Gwangse] Where? where?
[Devil's laughter]
[Leo/Russian] My black cat
[Devil] Really
[Urgent music]
[Seokchun] Who is this?
A cute little rat came hiding
Ugh, ah!
Hey, catch that bastard!
Hey, catch it!
[Hannah] Ugh!
[Seokchun] Hey!
I couldn't catch even one of those gannas
Do you have astigmatism?
Come to work!
[Hannah’s labored moans]
- Ha!
- [clap clap clap]
As expected, President Min!
Hahahaha
[Jooyoung] I, Mr.
It's a commemorative wine for the departure, but it's a waste.
- Look around.
- Hey
[Hannah] Ugh, ugh!
[Seokchun] Is there anything?
What, you don't even have a cell phone?
what?
Did you follow me here alone?
Is he brave or ignorant?
[Seokchun] Hey, stop
[Seokchun’s laughter]
Hey, you're prettier this way
- [Seokchun’s laughter]
- [Hannah] Ugh!
It's not pretty for you to see, put it away
Well, of course, it's attractive.
[Seokchun] Ha, ganna bastard
The temperament looks exactly like Nugi, huh?
Salty or whatever
When it rots, it's all just fish food.
I'll apply it all today
[Seokchun’s laughter]
[Devil] But
Seeing blood on the day of departure
Isn’t it a bit much?
unluckily
- I guess it's a bit like that.
- [Heavy music]
I even hit women
He's not that bad.
But I was a little embarrassed earlier.
inevitably
please understand
It must have hurt a little
[Seokchun] But President Min
What if I come this far and kill the child?
I have to send it to a good place
You'll like it too
It's a pretty cool place
It's such a nice place
It must be pretty expensive
[Jooyoung] Don’t worry
We know each other, but tickets are free.
There are quite a few empty seats.
[Hannah] Ugh, ugh!
- Ugh!
- [Organization member] Oh my!
[Jooyoung] I’m afraid I’ll be lonely alone
Because I can't speak
It won't be noisy
Thank you very much
[Jooyoung] The boat will shake a little.
Even if you don’t feel well, hold on for a while
It's narrow and there's no ventilation.
After about a week
You'll land in the middle of the Pacific Ocean
Floating on the sea like that
It will sink
If you're lucky enough to be alive by then
Please
Have a nice trip
It's very late, let's set sail at 3 o'clock.
Let me ask you one thing
Yeah, whatever.
In Inseong City in 2008
the russian mafia
There was an incident where he was shot and killed.
and
I was in charge of the case at that time
Not a single police officer
He was shot and killed
The name is
Ji Ho-cheol
[heavy music]
What does that have to do with you?
[sigh]
the dead cop
He's my father
No, why are you ending it?
No, this
Because Otala didn't kill him.
You don't even know where it is
Oh, so first look for it
Let's see if there's another culprit...
No, Russia...
Okay
[Calm music]
[Car starting sound]
[clack - gun]
[Squeak!]
[Boom! - Moon]
[clunk]
[Beep - Tea]
If the devil makes more candy
Because I have to send it to Japan
Please prepare
If we sell it all to Japan
What is this?
Until all the candy comes out
I have to keep my promise
That's the devil's
Because it was one of the conditions
Ha!
Don't sell to Korea
don't sell to kids
Damn, those are shit conditions.
I give it all out here and there
What do I do, just suck my fingers?
That won't happen
What do you mean?
[Jooyoung] Go until the end
Please check carefully
[Car starting sound]
[Meaningful music]
[Hannah] Ugh!
- [Organization Member] I, Mr.
- [Hannah] Let go of this!
[Organization members] Oh my!
[Knock Talk - Mobile Phone]
[Unstable call ring tone]
[Police/Noise] This is the 112 center.
How can we help you?
[Jonghyun] Yes, team leader
[Mansik] Uh, Sergeant Kim
A report was received at the 112 center.
I guess it looks like a police officer
[Meaningful music]
Uh, team leader, perhaps
Please confirm whether it is Geumpo Shipyard.
Uh, okay, just a moment...
[Gwangse] If it’s really true, it’s really awesome
[Mansik] Oh, it’s here, I’ll send it to you now.
[Hanna/recording/noise] Hello
This is Lieutenant Ji Hanna of the Inseong Police Agency.
Here is the location
Shipyard with a view of Inseong Bridge
Russian cargo ship Victory
It's inside the container.
Inseong Police Agency
Please tell this to team leader Go Man-sik.
All I can hear is Go Man-sik.
[Hanna/Recording] Hello? W...
[Too-to-too-too]
- [Jaehong] No, wait, wait...
- [Mansik] Hey
Inseong Bridge visible
shipyard
Shipyard with a view of Inseong Bridge
Geumpo Shipyard
It's Geumpo Shipyard.
Geumpo, that’s Geumpo Shipyard!
[Gwangse] Wow!
Wow, I found it, wow, awesome
Team leader, we're almost there.
[Mansik] Oh, I got it first.
It's Geumpo Shipyard.
Well, what I said in the recording earlier
The Russian ship Victory
I went into repairs
It's leaving at 3 o'clock today
I reported it
Let's go, are you going?
We must protect the investigation headquarters.
I'll be back
[Pawnshop owner] Don’t just look at the trees.
Look at the forest, forest!
- hello? Hey...
- [Cheolkeng - Moon]
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Nervous music]
[Hannah moans]
- [Organization member] Let’s go
- [Hannah] Ugh...
[Creak - door]
[clunk]
[Exciting music]
[Gwangse] I secretly shipped it from here.
Looks like he's leaving
Because the seagoing ship is undergoing repairs
When you enter the shipyard
Surveillance is becoming negligent.
Anyway
My liver is swollen, so openly
Hannah is over there.
If the ship departs at 3 o'clock
There's less than 20 minutes left
There are so many of them
How do I get in?
[Dongju] Wait a minute
Hey, can I go now?
I wish I was here
I'll help you
I don’t think there will be any, huh?
Yeah, go see it.
- Really?
- Are your legs okay?
I'm so fine
Oh, I can go by myself.
It's all better, look, bababak
[Dongju] Okay, then run
- [Gwangse] Huh?
-If you want to live
[Gwangse] Ugh! Ugh!
- [Nervous music]
- [Man] What are you?
[Gwangsae/Crying] I’m sorry
Ouch!
[noisy]
[Whispering] Now
[Jonghyun] I’ll go this way
you go over there
Hannah, Ji Hannah
Hannah, can you hear me? Jihanna
It's Hannah
It's Hannah, it's Hannah!
Jihanna!
It's Hannah
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
Hannah, can you hear me?
- [Thump thump thump]
- I'm here, it's Hannah!
Dongju?
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
If you can hear it, scream
Hannah, Ji-Hanna!
[Organizer/Russian] What are you doing here?
[Russian] What are you doing here?
Get out now!
Oh, be quiet.
It's Hannah!
Oh, wait.
- It's Hannah, it's Hannah!
- Yoon Dong-ju
[Organizer/Russian] Do you want to die?
Hey, you're so noisy
I can't hear you, really, shit, shit.
Well, where is Hannah?
Are you going to tell me?
It's here
Here!
here
- It's Hannah.
- [Hannah] Yoon Dong-ju
Jihanna
-Hannah, Jihanna
- [Hannah] I'm here
[Organization member] Hey
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
- [Hannah] I'm here
- It's Hannah.
- [Hannah] Here
It's Hannah, it's Hannah
- [Jonghyun] Where...
- If you hear a sound, scream.
- It's Hannah, it's Hannah.
- [The spirit of the organization members]
[Thump thump]
It's Hannah
Hannah, are you there?
[Hannah] Here it is
- here
-Hannah, it's here.
[Hannah] Here
[Calm music]
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Dongju] Ha...
It's okay
Sorry for being late
Are you okay, Hannah?
are you okay?
What is this million dollar face?
Wear these
[The spirit of the organization members]
Hurry up, gotta get down quick
[Pukpuk]
[Dongju] Take care of Hannah, Kim Jonghyun
It's Hannah
[Organization member] Oh my!
[Sigh!]
[Seokchun] Why?
Did you come here because you missed this taste, huh?
- Hahahaha!
- [Jonghyun] Ugh!
[Seokchun] Let’s finish it here, okay? 씨
[동주] 어이, 끝장은 나랑 봐야지
이 새끼가 진짜, 씨
[동주] 야
우리 애
건들지 말라고 했잖아, 어?
You bastard
Ugh!
Ouch!
Where are you going!
Open the door!
Hey, you bastard, open the door!
- are you okay?
- [Seokchun] Open the door
[stomping]
[Beep - Tinnitus]
[Calm music]
- [Jonghyun] Yoon Dong-ju, are you okay?
- [Eerie sound effect]
[Dongju moans]
Oh, there are so many seeds, what should I do?
Same in the ring
The moment you get scared, that's where it ends
[Dongju/Narration]
Being able to swallow fear
Unconditionally moving forward
[Dongju] You can move, right?
Take Hannah out
- And you?
- What should you do by yourself?
What to do
Because I found you
I have to run wild all the way
[intense music]
[The spirit of the organization members]
Go quickly!
[Organizer] Hey, catch it!
[Organization member] Ah!
Go quickly, get out quickly!
[nervous music]
[Heo Seong-jin, Diori’s ‘Night of Counting Stars’]
[Hannah] Stand, stand, senior
Kim Jonghyun!
[Devil] Things seem to be going wrong
[Mansik] Are you okay?
[Dongju] For helping me whenever I was having a hard time
Thank you
[Doctor] My condition
Don't take it lightly
[Hannah] Why didn’t you tell me?
[Dongju] This
[Hannah] Then I'm so sorry
I should have told you
[Mansik] To the police
Do you have any regrets about sticking with it?
[Jooyoung] You alone
No matter how hard I struggle
Nothing changes
You don’t know what day it is today, do you?
[Dongju] If you fall, just get up
I clenched my teeth
I will definitely catch you, I promise.
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]